Carlos Bruno Carvalho Moreira

Armação dos Búzios – RJ +55 (22) 98839-6545 | <u>brunobzs@gmail.com</u> <u>GitHub</u> | <u>LinkedIn</u>

OBJETCTIVE

QA Engineer, SDET, Automation or Mobile

SUMMARY

I am a OA with over 3 years of experience in the market. During this time, I developed skills in various technologies, including <u>JavaScript</u>, TypeScript, Cypress, Playwright, Postman, Git, Jira, SQL, Node.js, Linux, mobile tests (Android and iOS) and the Agile Scrum methodology.

I hold a degree in Production Engineering from Veiga de Almeida University and have a postgraduate degree in Software Engineering from Estácio de Sá University.

EDUCATION

- Bachelor's degree in production engineering Completed in 12/2014
- Postgraduate degree in Software Engineering Completed in 12/2022

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

JavaScript | TypeScript | Node.JS | Python | Cypress | Playwright | Git | Postman | Mobile Tests | Manual Tests | API Tests | Linux | Jenkins

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Personetics, USA – Mobile QA – 04/2024 to present - I work as a Mobile QA Engineer, focusing on ensuring the quality of our mobile applications. I work side by side with the R&D team, testing our apps on iOS and Android to deliver the best possible experience to users.

Shaw and Partners, USA - QA Engineer – 05/2023 to 04/2024 - Development of test cases, manual testing, and test automation. Ensure the excellence of the company's products or services. Conduct rigorous testing, identify and report defects, define quality standards, and collaborate with teams to improve processes. Ensure customer satisfaction and project success.

io.insure - USA, Australia, and the United Kingdom - QA Engineer Jr. - 01/2022 to 04/2023 - Manual testing, test automation, test analysis, TDD, validation of business rules, communication of risks, defects, and areas for possible improvements.